Finding Aid for the Jan Williams Collection of Annotated Scores, 1950-1999
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Kagel, Mauricio Match: für drei Spieler: 1964 / Mauricio Kagel Frankfurt ;New York: Henry Litolff's Verlag: C.F. Peters, [1964], 1 score (18 p.); 30 x 43 cm. (Box 9, Item 113)
  For 2 violoncellos and percussion. Publisher's reproduction of manuscript. Includes performance instructions. At end: Colonia, ii, i7/VIII/1964. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Kolb, Barbara Place settings Three place settings: for violin, clarinet, double bass, percussion, and narrator / Barbara Kolb New York: C. Fischer, c1972., 1 score (16 p.); 23 x 31 cm. (Box 9, Item 114)
  Reproduced from holograph. Inscription on verso of front cover from the composer to Jan Williams; accompanied by ms. letter (1 leaf) from composer to Jan Williams.
- Kwiatkowski, Ryszard, 1931- Quartets, percussion, no. 2 Quartet for percussion no. 2 / Ryszard Kwiatkowski Kraków: Polskie Wydawn. Muzyczne, c1971., 1 score (37 p.); 34 cm. (Box 9, Item 115)
  Duration: 17:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Laneri, Roberto, 1945- Dies Irae / Roberto Laneri. 1971., 1 ms. score (19 p.); 35 cm. (Box 9, Item 116)
  Holograph (Photocopy). Caption title. For voice, 2 horns, clarinet, bass clarinet, 2 violas, violoncello, double bass, and percussion (3 players). For violin, 2 pianos, 2 percussion groups, and narrator or self-prepared tape. Graphic notation. "Rome, July 1969-Buffalo, March 1971." Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Laneri, Roberto, 1945- The night brings a rabbit: for clarinet + percussion / Roberto Laneri; G. Schiaffini. 1971., 1 ms. score (8 leaves); 21 x 53 cm. (Box 9, Item 117)
  Holograph (Ozalid copy). Caption title. For voice (without text), clarinet, and percussion. "Dec. 1969/Jan. '70"--Caption. Includes performance instructions (leaf 8). Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Lepre, Robert Snare drum solo, no. 1 Snare drum solo: no. 1 / Robert Lepre New York, N.Y.: Music for Percussion, c1964., [3] p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 9, Item 118)
  Inscription on title page. from composer to Jan Williams.
- Levick, Hugh Embrace of reasonable terror. Selections The embrace of reasonable terror / Hugh Levick. [1986?], 1 ms. score (1-11, 1-12, 15-23, 69-92 leaves); 29 x 36 cm. + 1 ms. part (92 p.); 28 x 37 cm. (Box 9, Item 119)
  Holograph (Photocopy). Caption title. Five "opera sequences" to be performed as incidental music to Yves Reynaud's play, Les guerres froides. For voices (spoken and sung), saxophone (soprano, alto, and tenor), percussion, and piano. Words in English. Score marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams; piano part unmarked.
- Lockwood, Annea, 1939- Amazonia dreaming / Annea Lockwood [S.l.]: Sonic Art Editions, 1988., 1 ms. score ([2] leaves); 28 cm. (Box 9, Item 120)
  Holograph (Photocopy). For snare drum. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Lylloff, Bent Etudes, percussion, no. 10 Århus etude nr. 10: 6 players. Etude for percussion ensemble [Copenhagen]: Wilhelm Hansen, [c1970], 1 score ([3] p.) and 5 parts.; 30 cm. (Box 9, Item 121)
  Cover title. For triangle, tambourin, snare drum, cymbal, bass drum and timpani. Inscription on cover from the composer to Jan Williams.
- Macbride, David Quiet / David Macbride New York, N.Y.: American Composers Alliance, 1983., 1 ms. score (iv, 6 p.); 37 x 44 cm. (Box 9, Item 122)
  Holograph (Reproduction). Includes performance instructions. At end of score: 6/81, Sweet Briar, Va.; Rev. 5/83, Saratoga Springs, NY. Additional typescript list of revisions (1 leaf) inserted. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Mantel, Mark, 1961- Folk songs, clarinet, percussion (4) Folk songs / Mark Mantel. [1985], 7 ms. parts ([2] leaves each); 39 cm. (Box 10, Item 123)
  Title from verso of leaf [1]. Holograph (Photocopy). For clarinet (bass clarinet) and percussion (4 players). Parts marked for performance.
- Matamoros, Gustavo, 1957- In memory of gentle giant: for percussion and tape / Gustavo Matamoros. 1989., 1 ms. score (6 leaves); 29 x 44 cm. (Box 10, Item 124)
  Reproduced from holograph. "Written for Gordon Gottlieb." At end: March 15th, 1989. Duration 8:40. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Matamoros, Gustavo, 1957- Truly yours: for xylophone and taped ensemble / Gustavo Matamoros. [c1987], 1 ms. score (5 leaves); 23 x 36 cm. (Box 10, Item 125)
  Holograph (Photocopy). "Taped ensemble consisting of: drums, cymbals, vibes and DX-7." Duration: 6:14. Performance instructions preceding score. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974 Concertos, percussion, orchestra, op. 109; arr. Concerto pour batterie et petit orchestre / Darius Milhaud; réduction pour batterie et piano Wien: Universal Edition, 1958, c1931., 1 score (22 p.); 31 cm. (Box 10, Item 126)
  For 1 percussionist and piano; acc. originally for chamber orchestra. "Versione per 1 esecutore"--Caption, percussion part. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Miranda, Anthony Solos, drum set 11 solos for the drumset / by Anthony Miranda Ft. Lauderdale, FL: Music for Percussion, c1986., 36 p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 10, Item 127)
  Cover title. For five piece drum set (snare drum, small tom-tom, medium tom-tom, large tom-tom, bass drum) and cymbals.
- Miranda, Anthony Solos, drum set Eleven solos for the drum set / Anthony Miranda. [1979], 1 ms. score (unpaged); 30 cm. (Box 10, Item 128)
  Cover title. Holograph (Photocopy). "To my parents, fiancé, and to the following percussionists to whom I am indebted: Jan Williams, Dennis Walters, John Rowland, Jan Williams, Joe Morello, Jan Williams, Michael Pugliese, Jan Williams, Melissa Mediak, Lynn Harbold, Bent Lyloff."
- Miranda, Anthony Episodes, snare drum Two episodes for solo snare drum / Anthony Miranda Lancaster, NY: A.M. Percussion Publications, c1986., 3 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 10, Item 129)
- Miroglio, Francis Ping-squash: jeu sonore, pour 1 our 2 our 3 percussions / Francis Miroglio. [1980], 1 score + 2 parts (1 folded leaf each); 33 x 43 cm. (Box 10, Item 130)
  Musical game for two percussionists. Cover title. Score consists of performance instructions in French. Reproduced from manuscript. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Monaco, Alfredo del, 1938- Encuentros del eco--: para dos pianos y dos percusionistas / Alfredo del Monaco Caracas, Venezuela: Consejo Nacional de la Cultura, Instituto Latinoamericano de Investigaciones y Estudios Musicales "Vicente Emilio Sojo", 1979., 1 score (8 p.): port.; 39 cm. (Box 10, Item 131)
  Includes performance instructions in Spanish and English; biographical note in Spanish. Reproduced from holograph. At end: Berlin, I-V-76. Inscription on title page. from the composer to percussionist Jan Williams.
- Moss, Lawrence Incidental music: for percussion and mime/dancer / Lawrence Moss. 1986., 9 p. of ms. music; 36 cm. (Box 10, Item 132)
  Holograph (photocopy). At end: Malmantile (Firenze) 8/2/86. Duration: ca. 16:00. Inscription on title page. from the composer to percussionist Jan Williams.
- Newell, John, 1949- Prosody / John Newell. c1977., 1 ms. score (11 leaves); 37 cm. (Box 10, Item 133)
  Reproduced from holograph. Caption title. For solo percussion. Inscription on title page. from the composer to percussionist Jan Williams. At end: "Buffalo, March 1977."
- Nilsson, Bo Reaktionen: für 4 Schlagzeuger / Bo Nilsson; Auftragskomposition Radio Bremen; Faksimilereproduktion London: Universal Edition, [c1961], [3] p., score ([3]] p.; 31 cm. (Box 10, Item 134)
  For 4 performers, each with an identical assortment of percussion instruments. Performance instructions in German, French and English. Realization notes by percussionist Max Neuhaus (6 leaves) inserted.
- Nørgård, Per, 1932- I ching: percussion solo / Per Nørgård; [ed. by Gert Mortensen] Copenhagen: Edition W. Hansen ;New York: Edition W. Hansen/Chester Music: Distribution, Magnamusic-Baton, c1987., 49 leaves of music; 36 cm. (Box 10, Item 135)
- Nordheim, Arne Response, no. 1 Response 1: for two percussion groups and magnetic tape / Arne Nordheim København: Wilhelm Hansen, c1969., 1 score (16 leaves); 30 x 42 cm. (Box 10, Item 136)
  Duration: 16:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Ortiz, William Graffiti nuyorican: (para piano y percusión) / William Ortiz. c1984., 1 ms. score (14 leaves); 28 x 33 cm. (Box 11, Item 137)
  Holograph (Photocopy). At end: Alvarado 6-28-83. Percussion: 2 congas, claves, timbales, platillo, 2 cencerros, vibraphone, bongos, maraca. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Ortiz, William Street music: for flute, trombone and percussion = Música de la calle: para flauta, trombón y percusión / William Ortiz. [1980?], 1 ms. score (11 leaves); 28 x 36 cm. (Box 11, Item 138)
  Holograph (Ozalid copy). Performance instructions in English. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams; score also marked with alterations.
- Ortiz, William 124 E. 107th St.: for percussion, narrator-actor and electronic tape / William Ortiz. [1979], 1 ms. score (32 leaves); 32 x 38 cm. (Box 11, Item 139)
  Holograph (Ozalid copy). Texts by Pedro Pietri, and Sandra Esteves. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Ortiz, William Palm tree in Spanglish figurines: para 4 timpani / William Ortiz. [1987], 1 ms. score (7 leaves); 23 x 38 cm. (Box 11, Item 140)
  Holograph (Photocopy). At end: "William Ortiz - Alvarado 10/19/87." Duration: 11:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Pablo, Luis de A modo de concierto: per percussione e strumenti (1976) / Luis de Pablo. Milano: Edizioni Suvini Zerboni, c1977., 1 score (22 p.); 48 cm. (Box 11, Item 141)
  For percussionist solo, piano, celesta, glockenspiel, 8 violins or two small electric organs, and 8 violoncelli or two small electric organs. Reproduced from holograph. Inscription on title page. from the composer to percussionist Jan Williams.
- Pablo, Luis de Le prie-dieu sur la terrasse: per un percussionista / Luis De Pablo Milano: Suvini Zerboni, c1977., 11 ms. leaves of music; 29 x 43 cm. (Box 11, Item 142)
  Holograph (Ozalid copy). Chance composition. Diagrammatic notation. Duration: 17:10. "Octobre-Diciembre 1973, Buffalo (N.Y.)." Inscription on title page. from the composer to percussionist Jan Williams.
- Pablo, Luis de Saturno: per due percussionisti (1983) / Luis de Pablo Milano: Suvini Zerboni, c1983., 2 scores (14 p. each); 35 cm. (Box 11, Item 143)
- Pecquet, Frank Marianna: trio for guitar, cello and percussion / Frank Pecquet. 1987., 1 ms. score ([I], 14 leaves); 28 x 44 cm. (Box 11, Item 144)
  Holograph (Photocopy). For amplified guitar, cello, and percussion (one player). Caption title. Includes performance instructions in English, p. [I]. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Penner, Bruce The bears of Elisha: percussion duo / by Bruce Penner Fort Lauderdale, Fla. (170 N.E. 33rd St., Ft. Lauderdale, FL 33334): Music for Percussion, c1980., 2 scores (6 p. each); 31 cm. (Box 11, Item 145)
  Cover title. Includes instructions for performance. Marked (minimally) for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Rimmer, John, 1939- Clouds over Pirongia: for percussion quartet / John Rimmer Auckland: Catena Press, [1984], 1 score (6 p.); 32 cm. (Box 11, Item 146)
  Caption title. Inscription on caption from the composer to percussionist Jan Williams. Reproduced from manuscript. At end: "Cambridge N.Z. January, 1984."
- Chadabe, Joel [Valentine / Joel Chadabe]. [1989?], 3 ms. leaves); 28 cm. (Box 11, Item 147)
  For computer and percussion. Instructions by Jan Williams for performance of Joel Chadabe's composition, Valentine (2 leaves) and lead sheet (photocopy) of song by Richard Rodgers, My funny valentine (1 leaf).
- Rolnick, Neil B. Ever-livin' rhythm / by Neil B. Rolnick. c1978., 1 ms. score (7 leaves); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 11, Item 148)
  Holograph (Photocopy). For solo percussion (including marimba, vibraphone), and tape. Duration: 10:00. Includes performance instructions and drawing of stage set-up. At end: 1977, Berkeley, Stanford, Paris. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Rosen, Jerome, 1921- Elegy, percussion Elegy: for solo percussion / Jerome Rosen. 1963., 3 ms. leaves of music; 36 cm. (Box 11, Item 149)
  Holograph (Ozalid copy). Caption title. In caption of p. [1]: For Stan Lunetta. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams, including diagram of stage set-up.
- Rosenboom, David Continental divide: Denver, 1964 / David Rosenboom. c1964., 1 leaf of ms. music; 28 cm. (Box 11, Item 150)
  Caption title. Holograph (Photocopy). For 1 or more pianos, or pitched mallet instruments. Three copies included. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Rotter, Jorge Variations, percussion ensemble Variaciones: 1965: para 4 grupos de percusión / [Jorge Rotter]. 1965., 3 ms. parts; 42 cm. (Box 12, Item 151)
  Caption title. Holograph (Ozalid copy). Percussion II part wanting. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Ruders, Poul, 1949- Cha-cha-cha: a one man show for Jan Williams / Poul Ruders. 1981., 1 ms. score (A-C, 6 leaves): ill.; 36 x 46 cm. (Box 12, Item 152)
  Holograph (Photocopy). For solo percussion. "Final part of a trilogy of compositions all dealing with Latin American rhythms and percussion instruments." Includes performance instructions. At end: August CPH, 81. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Ruders, Poul, 1949- Wind-drumming / Poul Ruders. 1979., 1 ms. score (52 leaves): ill.; 42 cm. (Box 12, Item 153)
  For amplified flute, oboe (English horn), clarinet, horn, bassoon, and percussion (4 players). Holograph (Photocopy). Duration: ca. 11:30. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Rzewski, Frederic Lost and found: for Jan Williams / Frederic Rzewski. 1985., 1 ms. score (3 p.); 30 cm. (Box 12, Item 154)
  Holograph (Photocopy). Caption title. For 1 performer, speaking and acting. Score is in form of written instructions. "Text: Excerpt from letter home from Vietnam by Lieutenant Marion Lee (Sandy) Kempner of Galveston, Texas, August 7, 1966, as reprinted in N.Y. Times, Oct. 1, 1984." Duration: 9:00-15:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Rzewski, Frederic Les moutons de Panurge / Rzewski. [1969?], 1 ms. leaf of music; 28 cm. (Box 12, Item 155)
  Holograph (Photocopy). Includes performance instructions. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams. Extra, marked copy inserted.
- Rzewski, Frederic To the earth / Frederic Rzewski. 1985., 5 leaves of ms. music; 31 cm. (Box 12, Item 156)
  Holograph. Caption title. For speaking percussionist; text from a Homeric hymn. Words in English. Includes photocopies of leaves 2-5, with alterations to the music. "4/85"--Caption. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Sahl, Michael, 1934- Five piece / Michael Sahl. [196-?], 1 ms. score (16 p.); 37 cm. + 1 ms. part (14 p.); 34 cm. (Box 12, Item 157)
  Caption title. Holograph (Ozalid copy). For vibraphone, guitar, percussion (1 player), double bass, and piano. Missing final page(s). Part for mallets, guitar, bass, with cues for piano part. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Sahl, Michael, 1934- The last elms of Bidwell Parkway: 1991 / Michael Sahl. 1991., 1 ms. score (13 leaves); 44 cm. (Box 12, Item 158)
  Caption title. Holograph (Photocopy). For piano and percussion (1 player). At end: 1/30/91. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Sahl, Michael, 1934- Vibraphone piano and percussion piece / Michael Sahl. [1961], 1 ms. score (9 p.); 36 cm. (Box 12, Item 159)
  Caption title. Holograph (Ozalid copy). Includes performance instructions. At end: Dec. 6, 1961, Montuipaldi. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Samkopf, Kjell, 1952- Ingoma: variations on a drum solo from Burundi, Africa; for percussion quintet = Variasjoner over en trommesolo fra Burundi, Afrika; for slagverkkvintett / Kjell Samkopf Oslo: Musikk-Husets Forlag A/S, c1989., 1 score (36 p.) + 5 parts; 31 cm. (Box 12, Item 160-161)
  Commissioned by the Norwegian Band Federation. First performed on November 29, 1986 at the Munch Museum, Oslo, Norway. Duration: ca. 7:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Samkopf, Kjell, 1952- Variasjoner over Parang chant Variations on Parang Chant: for percussion sextett = Variasjoner over parang chant: for slagverksekstett / Kjell Samkopf Oslo: Musikk-Husets Forlag A/S, [1985], 1 score (32 p.) + 6 parts; 32 cm. (Box 12, Item 162-163)
  Title page inscribed and signed by composer. Publisher's plate number on first page of music only. Commissioned by the Norwegian Percussion Society. First performed on February 27, 1983 at the Hovikodden Art Centre, Oslo, Norway. Duration: ca. 10:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Scelsi, Giacinto, 1905-1988 Okanagon: per arpa, contrabasso e Tam-tam / Giacinto Scelsi. c1968., 1 ms. score (16 p.); 36 cm. (Box 12, Item 164)
  Ms. (Ozalid copy). Cover title. Inscription on title page. from the composer to Morton Feldman. Performance instructions in Italian. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams. Photocopy of score with markings on harp part inserted.
- Shapey, Ralph, 1921-2002 Evocation, no. 1 Evocation: no. 1 for violin, with percussion and piano (three scores are required for performance) / Ralph Shapey Bryn Mawr, Pa. (Bryn Mawr, Pa. 19010): T. Presser, c1984., 3 scores (41 p. each); 31 cm. (Box 13, Item 165)
  Duration: ca. 18:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Shapey, Ralph, 1921-2002 Gottlieb duo: for piano & percussion, 9/27/84-11/27/84 / Ralph Shapey. 1984., 1 ms. score (30 p.); 36 cm. (Box 13, Item 166)
  Holograph (Photocopy). "Commissioned by and dedicated to Gordon Gottlieb." Label on cover: Theodore Presser Company, Bryn Mawr, Pennsylvania. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams. Additional photocopies of 6 pages for use on glockenspiel stand.
- Simons, Netty Design groups: for percussion (1967); for 1 to 3 players / Netty Simons. 1967., 1 score ([1] folded leaf); 28 x 34 cm. (Box 13, Item 167)
  Reproduced from holograph. In part, graphic notation. Duration: 5-7:00. Stamp in caption: "Rental material, Property of Theodore Presser Company, Bryn Mawr, PA." Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Singer, Lawrence Concertos, violin, chamber orchestra [Untitled work for violin solo, percussion, woodwinds, and strings] / Lawrence Singer. c1968., 1 ms. score (34 p.); 39 cm. (Box 13, Item 168)
  Holograph (Ozalid copy). At end of score: September, 1966, E. Detroit, Michigan. Score marked for performance.
- Skiba, Norman, 1953- Noh: 4/5/86 / Norman Skiba. 1986., 1 ms. score (2 leaves); 25 x 38 cm. (Box 13, Item 169)
  For percussion (1 player). Caption title. Holograph (Photocopy). Includes performance instructions. Contains some markings by percussionist Jan Williams. Second photocopy of score (2 leaves; 16 x 25 cm.) with some differences in notation inserted
- Smit, Leo, 1921-1999 Cock robin / Leo Smit. 1979., 1 ms. score (25 leaves) + 1 ms. part; 35 cm. (Box 13, Item 170)
  Holograph (Photocopy). Title from holograph voice part. For soprano, piccolo (or flute) and percussion. Words in English. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams; also marked with changes to the score. At end of score: Sept. 22, 1979.
- Speach, Bernadette, 1948- Trajet / Bernadette Speach. 1983., 2 ms. scores (6 leaves each); 36 x 55 cm. (Box 13, Item 171)
  Holograph (Photocopy). For trombone and percussion (1 player). At end of score: 8/22/83. Additional leaf with diagram of stage setup inserted. Both scores marked for performance, one by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Stiebler, Ernstalbrecht, 1934- Im Takt--: für zwei kleine Bongos (1997) / Ernstalbrecht Stiebler Karlsruhe: Tre Media, c1998., 5 leaves of music; 29 x 41 cm. (Box 13, Item 172)
  Caption title. Reproduced from holograph. "Original, see revisions of 11/99 on copy"--Leaf 1.
- Stiebler, Ernstalbrecht, 1934- Im Takt--: (1997) / Ernstalbrecht Stiebler. 1997., 2 leaves of music; 22 x 36 cm. (Box 13, Item 173)
  Caption title. For two bongos, tuned approximately a fifth apart. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams; also marked with changes to score.
- Stiebler, Ernstalbrecht, 1934- Im Takt--: für zwei kleine Bongos (1997) / Ernstalbrecht Stiebler Karlsruhe: Tre Media, c1998., 5 leaves of music; 28 x 35 cm. (Box 13, Item 174)
  Caption title. Reproduced from holograph. "Rev. by ES 11/18/99"--Leaf 1. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams. Also inserted: photocopy of typescript notes to Jan Williams (2 leaves); photocopy of ms. note to Jan Williams (1 leaf); two reduced photocopies of leaf 3 and one reduced photocopy of leaf 4 of the score.
- Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007 Plus minus: 2 x 7 Seiten für Ausarbeitungen, Nr. 14 / Karlheinz Stockhausen. [1965?], 7 folders of music (Box 13, Item 175)
  Compilation of scores and musical materials for performance realization by Jan Williams, Edward Burnham, and Cornelius Cardew. Title from Universal Edition score. For 1 or several performers.
- Williams, Jan, 1939- Spiral / Stockhausen. [1973 or after], 5 ms. leaves; 28 cm. (Box 14, Item 176)
  Caption title. Spiral is a composition by Karlheinz Stockhausen for vocal or instrumental soloist and short-wave radio. Electronic amplification and other electronic devices may also be used. These ms. notes were written by percussionist Jan Williams in preparation for performance of the piece.
- Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971 Histoire du soldat L'Histoire du soldat = The soldier's tale / by Igor Stravinsky; edited by Frank Epstein [S.l.]: F. Epstein, c1995., 1 part (23 p.); 28 cm. (Box 14, Item 177)
  Ballet for narrator, 3 actors, and septet (clarinet, bassoon, cornet, trombone, violin, double bass, and percussion). Percussion part. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Swift, Richard, 1927- Domains, no. 2 Domains II: Op. 30 [for] solo percussion / Richard Swift [S.l.], 1963., 1 ms. score ([16] leaves); 31 cm. (Box 14, Item 178)
  Reproduced from ms. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Tenney, James Pika-don = Flash-boom / James Tenney. 1991., 1 ms. score (84 p.); 28 x 43 cm. (Box 14, Item 179)
  Holograph (Photocopy). For four percussionists and four-track tape. Includes performance instructions. "Commissioned by the Center for Contemporary Arts in Santa Fe, New Mexico, for the University of New Mexico Percussion Ensemble." Duration: 14:00. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Tenney, James Pika-don = Flash-boom / James Tenney. 1991., 1 ms. score (84 p.); 28 x 43 cm. (Box 14, Item 180)
- Tenney, James Rune / James Tenney. 1988., 1 ms. score (40 p.); 28 x 43 cm. (Box 14, Item 181)
  Holograph (Photocopy). For 5 percussionists. Duration: 20:00. Diagrammatic notation. Commissioned by the Nexus Percussion Ensemble with a grant from the Canada Council. Includes performance instructions. Additional photocopies of even-numbered pages inserted to eliminate page turns. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Tremblay, Gilles Le sifflement des vents porteurs de l'amour: pour flu^te et percussion / Gilles Tremblay. 1971., 1 ms. score (12 leaves); 39 cm. (Box 14, Item 182)
  Caption title. Holograph (Photocopy). Includes performance instructions. At end: Montréal, le 24 fevrier 1971. Marked for performance by percussionist Jan Williams.
- Trythall, Richard Bolero, percussion ensemble Bolero: for 4 percussionists / Richard Trythall. [1979]., 4 ms. scores (18 p. ea.); 30 x 42 cm. (Box 14, Item 183)